Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Ad Valorem Taxes
    - Electric Building and Kirby Theatre Building, First City National Bank, 1958-1969 (Box 236, Folder 23)
    - Ector and Midland Co., McKnight Bros, Roy Parks, and Sam Tuab Estate, 1953-1973 (Box 236, Folder 24)
    - Ector and Midland Co., McKnight Bros, Roy Parks, and Sam Tuab Estate, 1953-1973 (Box 236, Folder 25)
    - Bond's Store, 1950-1973 (Box 236, Folder 26)
    - Loew's State Theatre, 1928-1973 (Box 236, Folder 27)
    - Metropolitan Theatre, 1951-1973 (Box 236, Folder 28)
    - Simm's Lot, 802 San Jacinto, Houston, Orval Parker, 1958-1972 (Box 236, Folder 29)
    - Pioneer, Rusk, and Foster, 1957-1972 (Box 236, Folder 30)
    - Worth Theatre, 1951-1966 (Box 236, Folder 31)
    - Texas Electric Service, Ft. Worth, 1958-1972 (Box 236, Folder 32)
    - Texas Electric Service, Ft. Worth, 1958-1968 (Box 236, Folder 33)
  - Victoria County
    - Land Leases (Lake Placedo), 1932-1938 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Marilou Field, Lake Placedo Plantation Lands, 1963-1985 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Walker County
    - Bankers Mortgage Co. Timber Rights, Various Leagues and Surveys, Eastman to Humphrey, 1927-1938 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Waller County
    - Krueger Loan, T. Bell Surveys, 1927-1943 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Waller and Washington Counties
    - Land Leases, 1933-1939 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Washington County
    - Cox Property, Gibbon Kuykendall, 3/4 League Gant, 1916-1939 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - A.D. Milroy Estate, 1927-1928 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Land Leases, 1937 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Isaac Jackson League, 1941 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Webb County
    - Sn Johnson Land, Laredo, Texas, 1923-1947 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Sn Johnson Land, Laredo, Texas, 1924-1943 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - A. Johnson Land, Porciones 6 and 7, 1926-1938 (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Land Leases, 1936-1938 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Islitas Farm, Trevino Loan, 1945 (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Sn Johnson Land, Isopachous Maps, 1945-1971 (Box 237, Folder 15)
    - Consolidation Oil and Gas, 288.2 Acres Sold to H.G. Samuels, 1977-1988 (Box 237, Folder 16)
    - Laredo Field, Gulf Oil Corp., 1977-1991 (Box 237, Folder 17)
    - Laredo Field, Gulf Oil Corp., 1977-1991 (Box 237, Folder 18)
    - Laredo Field, Gulf Oil Corp., 1977-1991 (Box 237, Folder 19)
    - Laredo Field- Morganent, Inc. 1,237.8 Acres sold to HG Samuels, GED Link Lease, 1978-1984 (Box 237, Folder 20)
    - MMA Cattle Co. #1, 1979-1989 (Box 237, Folder 21)
    - Laredo Field, Good Hope Refineries, Inc., Sn Johnson Lands and GF and Sf Surveys, 1988-1991 (Box 237, Folder 22)
    - Laredo Field, Sanchez- O'Brien Oil and Gas Co., 1988-1992 (Box 237, Folder 23)
    - Laredo Field, TDC Eng. Co., 1990-1991 (Box 237, Folder 24)
  - Jim Wells County
    - Alice Oil Field, 1938-1939 (Box 237, Folder 25)
    - Alice Oil Field- WD Walton and EH Wicker, 1939-1962 (Box 237, Folder 26)
    - Alice Oil Field: Bryan and Saner Clegg Land, 1939-1963 (Box 237, Folder 27)
    - Alice Oil Field, 1940-1962 (Box 237, Folder 28)
    - Alice Oil Field: Gas Sales, 1951-1957 (Box 237, Folder 29)
    - Alice Oil Field: Gas Sales, 1951-1957 (Box 237, Folder 30)
    - Alice Oil Field: Gulf States Development Co. Mosser and Golapp, 1958-1975 (Box 237, Folder 31)
    - Alice Oil Field: CLA-BAR Oil and Gas Co., 1975-1979 (Box 237, Folder 32)
    - Alice Oil Field: The Oil and Gas Co., 1982 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Alice Oil Field: Spacing Exception, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Alice Oil Field: Well #1 Gulf States Dev. Co. ABTEX, Inc., 1975-1986 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Alice Oil Field: "A" Lease, Cleggland Tom Graham Pipe Line Statements, 1938-1948 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Alice Oil Field: "A" Lease, Atlantic Refining, 1939-1960 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Alice Oil Field: "A" Lease, Osborn and Fleet, 1939-1973 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Alice Oil Field: "B" Lease, Clegg Lanno, Tom Graham Pipe Line Statements, 1938-1951 (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Alice Oil Field: "B" Lease, Atlantic Refining Co., 1939-1948 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Alice Oil Field: "B" Lease, Osborn and Fleet, 1939-1948 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Alice Oil Field: "B" Lease, Mosser and Goldapp, 1961-1971 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Alice Oil Field: "C" Lease, W.B. Jewel Osborn, 1952-1974 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Alice Oil Field: "D" Lease, Atlantic Refining Co., 1939-1951 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Alice Oil Field: "A, B, C, D" Leases, W.H. Doran, Jr., 1961-1967 (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Alice Oil Field: "E" Lease, 1939-1963 (Box 238, Folder 14)
    - Alice Oil Field: "G" Lease, 1939-1963 (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - Alice Oil Field: "A, B, C, D, E, and G" Leases, Coastal States, 1962 (Box 238, Folder 16)
    - Alice Oil Field: "H" Lease, Clegg Lands, 1939-1958 (Box 238, Folder 17)
    - Alice Oil Field: "M" Lease, 1939-1951 (Box 238, Folder 18)
    - Clegg Lands, Mosser, and Goldapp Lease, PS Joseph Sub-Divison, 1962-1963 (Box 238, Folder 19)
    - GB Clegg Land, Lavaca Survey, Tom Graham Field, 1919-1947 (Box 238, Folder 20)
    - GB Clegg Land, Lavaca Survey, Alice Oil Field, 1929-1945 (Box 238, Folder 21)
    - GB Clegg Land, Lavaca Survey, Tom Graham Field, 1939-1983 (Box 238, Folder 22)
    - GB Clegg Land, Lavaca Survey, Alice Recycling Pool, 1942-1947 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - GB Clegg Land, Lavaca Survey, Alice Recycling Pool, 1942-1947 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Alice Oil Field, Texas Energy Exploration, Clegg Lands, 1978-1985 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Alice Oil Field, Texas Energy Exploration, Clegg Lands, 1978-1985 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Tom Graham Pool, 1948-1971 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Tom Graham Field, "T" Lease, Houston Natural Gas Production Co., 1961-1972 (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Tom Graham Field, Central Producers, Inc., 1974-1992 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Tom Graham Field, Central Producers, Inc., 1974-1992 (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - Tom Graham Field, Production, 1981-1983 (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Land Leases, 1932-1943 (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - Mannering Land, Latina Ja De Lara Grant, 1924-1959 (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - W.W. Thigpen Lands, Lavaca Grant, 1925-1942 (Box 239, Folder 12)
    - W.W. Thigpen Lands, Lavaca Grant, 1925-1948 (Box 239, Folder 13)
    - W.W. Thigpen Lands, PS Joseph Sub-Divison, Lavaca Grant, 1962-1988 (Box 239, Folder 14)
  - Williamson County
    - Lancaster Loan, Thos. E. Shell League, 1920-1944 (Box 239, Folder 15)
    - Land Leases, 1934-1942 (Box 239, Folder 16)
  - Zavalle County
    - GATO Creek Pasture, 1916 (Box 239, Folder 17)
  - Alabama
    - Block 233, 7th Ave. and 20th St., 1929-1931 (Box 239, Folder 18)
    - Block 233, 7th Ave. and 20th St., 1929-1931 (Box 239, Folder 19)
  - Louisiana
    - MT Jones Property, Bel Lumber Co., 1888-1916 (Box 239, Folder 20)
    - MT Jones Property, Cal Casieu Parish, Inventory, 1893 (Box 239, Folder 21)
    - Calcasieu Parish, 1918 (Box 239, Folder 22)
    - Calcasieu Vernon Parish, JM West - JH Jones Agreement, 1909 (Box 239, Folder 23)
    - Claiborne Parish, 1919-1922 (Box 239, Folder 24)
    - Claiborne Parish Abstract, 1920 (Box 239, Folder 25)
    - Gibsland, 1890-1917 (Box 239, Folder 26)
    - Gibsland, 1918-1932 (Box 239, Folder 27)
    - Gibsland, 1946-1948 (Box 239, Folder 28)
    - Gibsland, 1951-1958 (Box 239, Folder 29)
    - MT Jones Property, Pinelands Settlement, 1900-1903 (Box 239, Folder 30)
    - MT Jones Property, Pinelands Sale, 1905 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts
    - Springfield, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - New Mexico
    - Quay County, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - New York
    - 19 W 34th Street, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - 39th St. and Madison Ave. (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - 10 E. 40th Street, Near 5th Ave., 1933 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - 7th Ave at 53rd Street Craig Theater, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - 400 East 57th Street Sale, 1943-1957 (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - 400 E 57th Street at 1st Ave., 1947-1954 (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - 400 East 57th- Insurance Settlement, 1957-1958 (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - E. 61 Street (Leroy Sanitarium), 1946 (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - 277 Madison Ave. at 40th Street, 1929-1931 (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - Mayfair House, 612 Park Ave. Corp., 1946-1956 (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Mayfair House, 1948-1955 (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - Mayfair House- Sale, 1949-1978 (Box 240, Folder 15)
    - Mayfair House- Sale, 1949-1978 (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - Mayfair House- Equipment Depreciation, 1961-1971 (Box 240, Folder 17)
    - Mayfair House, 1959 (Box 240, Folder 18)
    - 812 Park Ave at 75th, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 19)
    - 950 5th Ave at 76th Street, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 20)
    - 1158 Fifth Ave., 1924-1927 (Box 240, Folder 21)
    - 1158 Fifth Ave., 1924-1927 (Box 240, Folder 22)
    - 1158 Fifth Ave. Apartment Sales, 1924-1929 (Box 240, Folder 23)
    - 200 Madison Ave, 39th, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 24)
    - Proposed 60 Story Building, 1929 (Box 240, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Various Buildings, 1947-1959 (Box 240, Folder 26)
    - Various Properties, 1929-1948 (Box 240, Folder 27)
    - Various Properties- Financing, 1932-1948 (Box 240, Folder 28)
    - Various Properties- Financing, 1932-1948 (Box 240, Folder 29)
    - Various Properties- Financing, 1932-1948 (Box 240, Folder 30)
    - Various Properties- Financing, 1932-1948 (Box 240, Folder 31)
  - Oklahoma
    - Oklahoma County, Block 34, 1900 (Box 240, Folder 32)
    - Perry, OK, Noble City, 1904-1908 (Box 240, Folder 33)
  - Tennessee
    - Sterick Building, Memphis, 1928-1930 (Box 240, Folder 34)
    - Sterick Building, 1929-1949 (Box 240, Folder 35)
    - Sterick Building, Memphis, 1930-1931 (Box 240, Folder 36)
  - Canada
    - Kingston, Ontario, n.d. (Box 240, Folder 37)
- Series III: Research for Unprecedented Power by Steven Fenberg
  - Photocopies
    - Photocopies, 1914-1928 (Box 241, Folder 1-3)
    - Photocopies, 1929-1939 (Box 242, Folder 1-5)
    - Photocopies, 1930s (Box 243, Folder 1-4)
    - Photocopies, 1941-1945 (Box 244, Folder 1-4)
    - Photocopies, 1944-1951 (Box 245, Folder 1-3)
  - Various Notes and Photocopies, 1800s-1990
    - Various Notes and Photocopies (Box 246, Folder 1-16)
    - Various Notes and Photocopies (Box 247, Folder 1-15)
    - Various Notes and Photocopies (Box 248, Folder 1-13)
    - Various Notes and Photocopies (Box 249, Folder 1-14)
    - Various Notes and Photocopies (Box 250, Folder 1-10)
  - Research Materials, 2000
    - Photocopies Old Tennessee Pix, 1900s (Box 250)
    - Photocopies, W. Wilson File, 1920s (Box 250)
    - Photocopies, W. Wilson File, 1920s (Box 250)
    - Notes (Box 250)
    - JHJ Notes (Box 250)
    - JHJ Quotes (X-Mas Cookies) (Box 250)
    - JHJ- FBI File (Box 250)
    - Information File on Jones (Box 250)
    - "Documentation" File, 1910s-1950s (Box 251)
    - "Documentation" File, 1910s-1950s (Box 251)
    - Democratic National Committee Financial Chairman, 1924 (Box 251)
    - FDR file, 1926-1939 (Box 251)
    - Public National Bank (Box 251)
    - Houston Banks, 1931 (Box 251)
    - Gold File, 1930s (Box 251)
    - BBallrooms, 1930s (Box 251)
    - Will Rogers, 1930s (Box 251)
    - Drew Pearson, 1933-1943 (Box 251)
    - Vice President, 1940 (Box 251)
    - Various Documents, 1940s-1950s (Box 251)
    - Harry Truman, 1947 (Box 251)
    - Arabian American Oil Co. James A. Moffett Suit Memo for Mr. Jones, 1948 (Box 251)
    - Interviews, 1990s (Box 252)
    - Clippings, 2005-2008 (Box 252)
    - "Maybe" File (Box 252)
    - "Maybe Need" File, 1940s (Box 252)
    - Extras "File" (Box 252)
    - Extras "File" (Box 252)
    - Extras "File" (Box 252)
    - Jones Notebooks (6) (Box 253, Envelope 1-4)
    - Estate Check, 1956 (Box 253, Envelope 5)
    - Fortune Magazines, 1940 (Box 253, Envelope 6)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1940 (Box 253, Envelope 7)
    - Life Magazine FDR Commemorative Issue, 1940; 2000 (Box 253, Envelope 8)
    - Robertson County Times, Remembering the Millenium, 2000 (Box 253, Envelope 9)